{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "prompt": "In which part of your body would you find the cruciate ligament?",
      "options": [
        "Ankle",
        "Knee",
        "Elbow",
        "Wrist"
      ],
      "answer": "Knee"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "prompt": "What element is denoted by the chemical symbol Sn in the periodic table?",
      "options": [
        "Tin",
        "Sulfur",
        "Silicon",
        "Sodium"
      ],
      "answer": "Tin"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "prompt": "What was the most popular girls name in the UK in 2021?",
      "options": [
        "Sophia",
        "Emma",
        "Amelia",
        "Olivia"
      ],
      "answer": "Olivia"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "prompt": "What is the name of the 1976 film about the Watergate scandal, starring Robert Redford and Dustin Hoffman?",
      "options": [
        "The Post",
        "Frost/Nixon",
        "The Candidate",
        "All the President's Men"
      ],
      "answer": "All the President's Men"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "prompt": "Which popular video game franchise has released games with the subtitles World At War and Black Ops?",
      "options": [
        "Halo",
        "Call of Duty",
        "Battlefield",
        "Medal of Honor"
      ],
      "answer": "Call of Duty"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "prompt": "What is the currency of Denmark?",
      "options": [
        "Pound",
        "Franc",
        "Krone",
        "Euro"
      ],
      "answer": "Krone"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "prompt": "Which Tennis Grand Slam is played on a clay surface?",
      "options": [
        "Wimbledon",
        "French Open",
        "US Open",
        "Australian Open"
      ],
      "answer": "French Open"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "prompt": "In which European country would you find the Rijksmuseum?",
      "options": [
        "Netherlands",
        "Germany",
        "Belgium",
        "France"
      ],
      "answer": "Netherlands"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "prompt": "What was the old name for a Snickers bar before it changed in 1990?",
      "options": [
        "Mars",
        "Milky Way",
        "Marathon",
        "Twix"
      ],
      "answer": "Marathon"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "prompt": "Who was the head of state in Japan during the second world war?",
      "options": [
        "Emperor Akihito",
        "Prime Minister Abe",
        "Prime Minister Tojo",
        "Emperor Hirohito"
      ],
      "answer": "Emperor Hirohito"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "prompt": "What is the smallest planet in our solar system?",
      "options": [
        "Mercury",
        "Venus",
        "Pluto",
        "Mars"
      ],
      "answer": "Mercury"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "prompt": "Who wrote the novels Gone Girl and Sharp Objects?",
      "options": [
        "Jo Nesbo",
        "Paula Hawkins",
        "Liane Moriarty",
        "Gillian Flynn"
      ],
      "answer": "Gillian Flynn"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "prompt": "Which legendary surrealist artist is famous for painting melting clocks?",
      "options": [
        "Magritte",
        "Dali",
        "Kahlo",
        "Picasso"
      ],
      "answer": "Dali"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "prompt": "Which football club plays its home games at Loftus Road?",
      "options": [
        "Brentford",
        "Fulham",
        "Queens Park Rangers",
        "Crystal Palace"
      ],
      "answer": "Queens Park Rangers"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "prompt": "What was the Turkish city of Istanbul called before 1930?",
      "options": [
        "Bursa",
        "Constantinople",
        "Smyrna",
        "Ankara"
      ],
      "answer": "Constantinople"
    }
  ]
}
 